Contact

www.linkedin.com/in/varun-sharma (LinkedIn) varunsharma15.wordpress.com (Personal) github.com/Varun-Sharma-N/ (Portfolio)

Top Skills

Machine Learning
Data Science
Software Development

Certifications

2020 AWS SageMaker, Al and Machine Learning - With Python

Publications

Serialization and Deserialization of Python Objects using Pickle and cPickle Modules and their Performance Comparison

Web Browser Application-Test Automation Using Selenium Webdriver with Junit Framework

VARUN SHARMA N

Data Scientist with 1+ years of experience | Looking for new opportunities in Data Science and Machine Learning field.

Orange County, California Area

Summary

Graduated with Master's degree at California State University, Fullerton with an emphasis on Data Science and Machine Learning. I have worked on cost prediction and image classification kaggle projects.

Worked on Titan Rover project to develop an object detection model to help autonomous navigation function.

Experience

48WS

Data Scientist and Web Developer July 2019 - Present (9 months)

Tustin. CA

International Friendship Club, Cal State Fullerton Web Developer and IT Coordinator December 2017 - September 2018 (10 months) Fullerton, CA, USA

Designed and developed website for the club which has gallery, club information, etc. Managed other tasks like setting up online event registrations and managing email accounts.

48WS

Data Scientist and Web Developer Intern June 2018 - July 2018 (2 months)

Tustin, California

Analyzed and cleaned data using pandas and numpy. Developed interactive websites using PHP, HTML, CSS, JavaScript and WordPress.

Techno Crown Solutions

Lead Developer June 2016 - July 2017 (1 year 2 months)

Experience working as both full stack developer and in team. Developed Windows Desktop softwares using C#, Android apps and Wordpress sites. Mentored team members and assigned tasks.

Education

California State University, Fullerton Master's degree, Computer Science · (2017 - 2019)

Rajeev Institute of Technology
Bachelor of Engineering (BE), Computer Science · (2012 - 2016)